[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the surname of Tonys family featured in the movie Saturday Night Fever?", "correct_answer": "Manero", "incorrect_answers": ["Moffo", "DiVito", "Capo"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Thomas Lennon has stated that his favorite movie of all time is which one of these?", "correct_answer": "Brazil", "incorrect_answers": ["Out Cold", "Tommy Boy", "The Pacifier"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Conakry is the capital of Turkey.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where was the first wrapped candy bar sold?", "correct_answer": "Canada", "incorrect_answers": ["Georgia", "New York", "Pennsylvania"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Sapphire is usually associated with this month.", "correct_answer": "September", "incorrect_answers": ["November", "December", "October"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which is the only food that never spoils?", "correct_answer": "Honey", "incorrect_answers": ["Potatoes", "Pasta", "Peanut butter"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was Mias fathers name in the movie The Princess Diaries?", "correct_answer": "Phillipe Renaldi", "incorrect_answers": ["Louie Renaldi", "Rupert Renaldi", "Joe Renaldi"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The national epic poem of which country includes an early ode to beer in Verse XX: Sing the songs of beer immortal!?", "correct_answer": "Finland", "incorrect_answers": ["Denmark", "Sweden", "Germany"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What meat does a proper Irish breakfast usually include?", "correct_answer": "Pork", "incorrect_answers": ["It does not include meat.", "Beef", "Chicken"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This short-lived American sitcom aired on CBS in 1995, starring Andrew Dice Clay and Cathy Moriarty.", "correct_answer": "Bless This House", "incorrect_answers": ["Burt and Alice", "Ford Fairlane", "Healeys Class"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which two American cities boast statues of Popeye the Sailor?", "correct_answer": "Crystal City, Texas and Chester, Illinois", "incorrect_answers": ["Petaluma, California and Palm City, Florida", "Wiley, Texas and East St. Louis, Illinois", "Eureka, California and Kingsville, Texas"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How does the poor Moroccan goat herder get the rifle in the movie Babel?", "correct_answer": "He buys it for 500 dirhams and a goat.", "incorrect_answers": ["The tourists from Guatemala give it to him.", "He steals it from Richard.", "The tourists from Japan give it to him."]}]